http://www.edval.com.au/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Edval Timetables respects your privacy and is committed to protect the personal information that you share with us. This policy describes how we collect and use your personal information.
Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, email address, a school, postal or other physical address, other contact information, title, personal or product interests, other information when needed to provide a product or service you requested.
Edval Timetables collects information when we license your software, when you use our products, or send data to us for support purposes. Edval Timetables collects information when you register to attend a training course, when you ask to be included in an email or other mailing list, other product promotions, or when you submit your information to Edval Timetables for any other reason.
Edval Timetables uses information for several general purposes: to fulfil your requests for certain products and services, to support you in the use of our products, to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers or other information we think you’d like to hear about from us, and to better understand your needs and provide you with better services. We may also use your information to send you direct marketing information or contact you for market research.
Edval Timetables does not share your information with any third party, unless specifically requested to do so by you.
Edval Timetables will amend this policy from time to time.
If you have questions or concerns about our collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information, please email us at security@edval.education.
